<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
        <title>Digg Top Stories</title>
        <description>Digg - What the Internet is talking about right now</description>
        <link>http://digg.com/rss/top.rss</link>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2013 04:06:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2013 04:06:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <ttl>15</ttl>

         
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
        <item>
            <title>What It's Like To Write A Video Game</title>
            <description>Modern video games are showing signs of morphing into other, still more subtle and complicated forms; among other things, they’re becoming an increasingly sophisticated vehicle for storytelling.</description>
            <link>http://www.newyorker.com/online/blogs/books/2013/03/gears-of-war-writer-tom-bissell-on-video-games-and-storytelling.html</link>
            <guid>http://on.digg.com/15YCl57</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2013 19:58:41 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
         
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
        <item>
            <title>How To Get Out Of Quicksand</title>
            <description>Is it possible to survive being stuck in quicksand?</description>
            <link>http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=a2VJqud3Ls8&amp;feature=youtu.be&amp;t=1m12s</link>
            <guid>http://on.digg.com/WUhHmd</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2013 01:03:07 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
         
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
        <item>
            <title>The 'Canonical' Image Of A Drone Probably Isn't Real</title>
            <description>It’s the first Google image result for “drone” and as such is reproduced endlessly elsewhere. But it's probably a fake.</description>
            <link>http://onevisiblefuture.tumblr.com/post/44865882761/i-have-something-of-an-obsession-with-the-image</link>
            <guid>http://on.digg.com/Warcet</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2013 15:45:13 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
         
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
        <item>
            <title>Building The World's Largest Ship (In 76 Seconds)</title>
            <description>A timelapse of the construction of Maersk Line's very first Triple-E vessel at the DSME shipyard in Okpo, Korea.</description>
            <link>http://vimeo.com/channels/staffpicks/62085613</link>
            <guid>http://on.digg.com/XnI5jg</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2013 22:23:31 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
         
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
        <item>
            <title>Christo Presents The Largest Inflated Envelope In History</title>
            <description>Christo's &quot;Big Air Package&quot; is the largest ever inflated envelope without the aid of a skeleton. It may even be the largest indoor sculpture in history.</description>
            <link>http://www.thisiscolossal.com/2013/03/big-air-package-the-largest-inflated-envelope-in-history-by-christo/</link>
            <guid>http://on.digg.com/11axUFj</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2013 14:07:28 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
         
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
        <item>
            <title>The Gigantic Mosquitos Sent To Destroy Humanity</title>
            <description>Gallinippers, which go by the scientific name of Psorophora ciliata, are said to be about the size of a quarter with a painful bite that’s been described by some as getting stabbed with a knife.</description>
            <link>http://www.fastcodesign.com/1672126/the-gigantic-mosquitos-sent-to-destroy-humanity</link>
            <guid>http://on.digg.com/15nqoUs</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2013 20:22:56 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
         
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
        <item>
            <title>Feds: No Warrant Needed To Track Your Car With A GPS Device</title>
            <description>The Obama administration is claiming that authorities do not need court warrants to affix GPS devices to vehicles to monitor their every move.</description>
            <link>http://www.wired.com/threatlevel/2013/03/gps-warrant-requirement/</link>
            <guid>http://on.digg.com/15WvkSe</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2013 11:38:46 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
         
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
        <item>
            <title>The Most Realistic Virtual Human Ever Is A Fully Expressive Talking Head</title>
            <description>Hoping to be holding the personal assistant of the future, researchers at the University of Cambridge have unveiled what's supposedly the most realistically esxpressive controllable avatar ever. Move aside, Siri—this is what you get for mouthing off.</description>
            <link>http://gizmodo.com/5991365/the-most-realistic-virtual-human-ever-is-a-fully-expressive-talking-head</link>
            <guid>http://on.digg.com/138OS8j</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2013 18:49:21 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
         
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
        <item>
            <title>Slaves' Forgotten Burial Sites Are Now Being Marked Online</title>
            <description>They have been bulldozed over by shopping centers, crept over by weeds and forgotten by time. Across the country, from Lower Manhattan to the Deep South, are unmarked slave burial sites. Now the Burial Database Project of Enslaved African Americans is trying to change all that.</description>
            <link>http://cityroom.blogs.nytimes.com/2013/03/18/a-mission-to-find-and-preserve-forgotten-slave-graveyards/?smid=tw-nytmetro</link>
            <guid>http://on.digg.com/15mcHVA</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2013 14:44:37 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
         
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
        <item>
            <title>The Mother Of All Rooftopping Photos, On Top Of The Tallest Building In The World</title>
            <description>Famed National Geographic photographer Joe McNally managed to snap the mother of all rooftopping photos,</description>
            <link>http://www.petapixel.com/2013/03/19/the-mother-of-all-rooftopping-photos-on-top-of-the-tallest-building-in-the-world/</link>
            <guid>http://on.digg.com/Yp0JHE</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2013 21:22:42 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
         
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
        <item>
            <title>Dying Vet's 'F*ck You' Letter To George Bush And Dick Cheney</title>
            <description>You may evade justice but in our eyes you are each guilty of egregious war crimes, of plunder and, finally, of murder, including the murder of thousands of young Americans—my fellow veterans—whose future you stole.</description>
            <link>http://dangerousminds.net/comments/dying_vets_fuck_you_letter_to_george_bush_dick_cheney_needs_to_be_read</link>
            <guid>http://on.digg.com/10dREVW</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2013 19:23:10 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
         
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
        <item>
            <title>Who Is Guccifer, The Hacker Who's Terrorizing Politicos?</title>
            <description>An Illuminati-obsessed hacker is breaking into the email accounts of Washington, D.C.'s political elite, and sharing what he finds. Who is Guccifer, and what's his motive?</description>
            <link>http://gawker.com/5991331/who-is-guccifer-the-hacker-whos-terrorizing-politicos</link>
            <guid>http://on.digg.com/Y0Pqew</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2013 21:38:03 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
         
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
        <item>
            <title>The Iraq War Timeline As Told Through Front Pages</title>
            <description>From &quot;Shock and Awe&quot; to the insurgency to the Surge.</description>
            <link>http://www.buzzfeed.com/andrewkaczynski/the-iraq-war-timeline-as-told-through-front-pages</link>
            <guid>http://on.digg.com/11bY5Yp</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2013 22:09:49 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
         
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
        <item>
            <title>Google Calls For More Email Privacy In Congressional Testimony</title>
            <description>In testimony to be delivered to Congress today, Google's legal director Richard Salgado says the 1968 Electronic Communications Privacy act was good when it was enacted but that now &quot;the law fails to preserve the reasonable privacy expectations of Americans today.&quot;</description>
            <link>http://www.theverge.com/2013/3/19/4122848/google-testifies-congress-says-ecpa-email-privacy-law-fails</link>
            <guid>http://on.digg.com/XZvFnB</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2013 14:03:42 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
         
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
        <item>
            <title>NYC Pot Decriminalization Could Happen This Week</title>
            <description>Governor Coumo is pushing for the decriminalization of small amounts of pot in NYC, something that Mayor Bloomberg is in favor of.</description>
            <link>http://gothamist.com/2013/03/19/nyc_pot_decriminalization_could_hap.php</link>
            <guid>http://on.digg.com/11f42HP</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2013 19:08:12 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
         
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
        <item>
            <title>A Surprisingly Large Number Of Men Catch Their Genitals In A Zipper Every Year</title>
            <description>Zipper injuries are the single most common cause of penile injury in adult men reporting to emergency rooms.</description>
            <link>http://www.nbcnews.com/id/51248766/#.UUjnsluk-dB</link>
            <guid>http://on.digg.com/YENzFR</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2013 22:33:40 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
         
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
        <item>
            <title>What It Takes To Protect Obama On A Middle East Trip</title>
            <description>Ex-Secret Service agent Dan Emmett talks about what it takes to keep the president safe on a trip to the Middle East, where President Obama will arrive on Wednesday.</description>
            <link>http://www.thedailybeast.com/articles/2013/03/19/what-it-takes-to-protect-obama-on-a-middle-east-trip.html</link>
            <guid>http://on.digg.com/ZWxvBr</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2013 16:26:57 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
         
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
        <item>
            <title>People Will Think Less Of You When You Show Them Your BlackBerry Z10</title>
            <description>Are people looking down on BlackBerries, and the people who use them, as a proxy for resentment for people who are poor?</description>
            <link>http://betabeat.com/2013/03/people-will-think-less-of-you-when-you-show-them-your-blackberry-z10-david-shapiro/</link>
            <guid>http://on.digg.com/ZHbirb</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2013 17:06:54 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
         
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
        <item>
            <title>Am I A Torturer?</title>
            <description>Ben Allbright watches The Daily Show, worships Dave Eggers—and still wound up &quot;softening up&quot; prisoners in Iraq.</description>
            <link>http://www.motherjones.com/politics/2008/03/am-i-torturer</link>
            <guid>http://on.digg.com/39cMot</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2013 18:46:36 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
         
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
        <item>
            <title>March Madness Will Cost Businesses $134M. Why Aren’t Employers Concerned?</title>
            <description>A few decades ago, the idea that employees would be able to spend hours watching a sporting event during normal working hours would’ve been unthinkable.</description>
            <link>http://business.time.com/2013/03/19/march-madness-will-cost-businesses-134-million-why-arent-employers-concerned/?xid=rss-topstories&amp;utm_source=feedburner&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=Feed%3A+time%2Ftopstories+%28TIME%3A+Top+Stories%29</link>
            <guid>http://on.digg.com/16GA93B</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2013 12:27:12 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
         
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
        <item>
            <title>The Iffy Science Of Measuring Calories</title>
            <description>As you may have heard, sex doesn't burn nearly as many calories as you might have been led to believe. But this is far from the only finding in obesity research that wilts under intense scrutiny.</description>
            <link>http://www.theawl.com/2013/03/sex-and-lies-the-iffy-science-of-measuring-calories?utm_source=feedburner&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=Feed%3A+TheAwl+%28The+Awl%29</link>
            <guid>http://on.digg.com/ZbGBYR</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2013 19:27:59 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
         
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
        <item>
            <title>How Soccer Explains Israel</title>
            <description>Jerusalem's FC Beitar signed two Muslim players from Russia in February and — intentionally or not — stirred a national controversy.</description>
            <link>http://www.grantland.com/story/_/id/9066752/view/full/jerusalem-fc-beitar-signed-two-muslim-players-russia-february-stirred-national-controversy</link>
            <guid>http://on.digg.com/XnyFV3</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2013 21:19:03 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
         
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
        <item>
            <title>Which Country's Banks Have The Most Power To Destroy Their Economies?</title>
            <description>How do you find the next Cyprus, a country where the banks’ problems are imperiling the entire country’s economy?</description>
            <link>http://www.marketwatch.com/story/countries-most-exposed-to-their-banks-2013-03-19?siteid=rss&amp;utm_source=twitterfeed&amp;utm_medium=twitter</link>
            <guid>http://on.digg.com/YEIBJ8</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2013 21:42:54 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
         
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
        <item>
            <title>Five Myths About Iraq</title>
            <description>On the eve of the U.S. invasion of Iraq, the assumptions many Americans held about the coming war, fed by rhetoric from the George W. Bush White House, turned out to be wildly inaccurate. Today, a new set of beliefs defines many discussions about the war and its aftermath. Are they just as wrong?</description>
            <link>http://www.washingtonpost.com/opinions/five-myths-about-iraq/2013/03/15/f7a62a40-8772-11e2-9d71-f0feafdd1394_story.html?Post+generic=%3Ftid%3Dsm_twitter_washingtonpost</link>
            <guid>http://on.digg.com/16H3qed</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2013 17:11:44 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
         
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
        <item>
            <title>Brazilian Bikini Waxes Behind The Rise In STDs</title>
            <description>Shaving and waxing of bikini lines could be behind an explosion in the number of cases of a type of sexually transmitted infection that causes unsightly warts, doctors are warning.</description>
            <link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/health/healthnews/9938288/Bikini-waxes-and-Brazilians-behind-rise-in-STI-warts.html</link>
            <guid>http://on.digg.com/11daeAd</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2013 17:48:10 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
         
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
        <item>
            <title>Powerful Tornadoes Can Transport Photographs Over 200 Miles</title>
            <description>And this is the story of how a Facebook group became the best dataset on tornado debris ever created.</description>
            <link>http://www.theatlantic.com/technology/archive/13/03/powerful-tornadoes-can-transport-photographs-over-200-miles/274154/</link>
            <guid>http://on.digg.com/XnF829</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2013 18:15:36 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
         
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
        <item>
            <title>What Happens In An Internet Minute?</title>
            <description>204 million emails are sent, six million Facebook pages are viewed and 1.3 million YouTube clips are downloaded.</description>
            <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-2295703/What-happens-Internet-minute-6m-Facebook-pages-viewed-1-3m-YouTube-clips-downloaded-.html?ITO=1490&amp;ns_mchannel=rss&amp;ns_campaign=1490</link>
            <guid>http://on.digg.com/WB2FPQ</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2013 15:02:43 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
         
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
        <item>
            <title>Body Modification Legend Left This Final Note Before His Suicide</title>
            <description>Body modification enthusiasts may know better than most people what it's like to be judged on sight for their piercings, tattoos, scars, and other forms of body art. For Shannon Larratt, the founder of BMEzine, this societal judgment may have cost him the final years of his life.</description>
            <link>http://www.dailydot.com/society/bme-zine-shannon-larratt-suicide-note/</link>
            <guid>http://on.digg.com/145FBgq</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2013 16:53:22 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
         
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
        <item>
            <title>The House Across From Westboro Baptist Is Getting A Rainbow Pride Paint Job Right Now</title>
            <description>By the end of today, the inhabitants of the Westboro Baptist Church compound in Topeka, Kansas, should have a new view out their windows, just past their FAG MARRIAGE DOOMS NATIONS sign: a new gay-rights center across the street, painted in brilliant rainbow colors, with a pride flag flying from a 30-foot flagpole.</description>
            <link>http://gawker.com/5991291/the-house-across-from-westboro-baptist-is-getting-a-rainbow-pride-paint-job-right-now</link>
            <guid>http://on.digg.com/149Dxo9</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2013 16:53:14 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
         
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
        <item>
            <title>The Numbers Behind America's Most Expensive Fighter Jet Ever</title>
            <description>The F-35 Joint Strike Fighter is designed to do everythig from night stealth missions to tank destruction to vertical takeoff. Such prowess doesn't come cheap.</description>
            <link>http://www.popsci.com/technology/article/2013-03/numbers-americas-most-expensive-fighter-ever-infographic</link>
            <guid>http://on.digg.com/16GHArs</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2013 13:32:19 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
         
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
        <item>
            <title>Spring Break Is Big Business</title>
            <description>Spring break is, in the popular imagination, a time of freedom. But in actuality, spring break has become—like nearly everything else US college students do—an expensive, highly structured event that someone is making money off of.</description>
            <link>http://www.vice.com/read/spring-break-is-big-business</link>
            <guid>http://on.digg.com/WBBmFf</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2013 18:01:41 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
         
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
        <item>
            <title>The School Tuitions Of The NCAA Bracket</title>
            <description>Sure, winning a basketball title is worth bragging about, but we all know the real champion is the institution of higher education that can charge the most tuition and still have enough students to keep its rejection letter printer warm.</description>
            <link>http://www.theawl.com/2013/03/2013-march-madne-the-school-tuitions-of-the-ncaa-bracket?utm_source=feedburner&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=Feed%3A+TheAwl+%28The+Awl%29</link>
            <guid>http://on.digg.com/108OB1j</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2013 14:40:53 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
         
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
        <item>
            <title>Why All Of Your Favorite Shows Are Ratings Disasters</title>
            <description>The new rules of the hyper-social, data-driven, actor-friendly, super-seductive platinum age of television.</description>
            <link>http://www.wired.com/underwire/2013/03/nielsen-family-is-dead/</link>
            <guid>http://on.digg.com/WT04Df</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2013 13:02:07 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
 
</channel>
</rss>
